<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <missionname.tsmmission11>Border Case</missionname.tsmmission11>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission11>Since the opening of the Abyssal Gate, many uninvited visitors have come to the shallow waters of the Abyss. We marked them from a distance during the last confrontation, and this time, the signal was detected inside the territory of The Sea of Miracles. So, warriors, with swords in hand, let's fight to the end!</missiondescription.tsmmission11>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission11>Falling Stars</missionsuccess.tsmmission11>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission11>Recorded in Border Archive, No. 011.</missionheader0.tsmmission11>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission11>Our land is not to be trampled on by any hostile creature.</missionmessage0.tsmmission11>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission11>Spinning Star</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission11>
  <missionname.tsmmission12>Eclipse</missionname.tsmmission12>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission12>T.S.M is fighting in frontline Area 73 and has no time to worry about the safety of this area, but T.S.M guarantees a [reward] mk to the captain who kills these beasts.</missiondescription.tsmmission12>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission12>Congratulations, you made it!</missionsuccess.tsmmission12>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission12>Third Contact of Eclipse</missionheader0.tsmmission12>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission12>What a bright performance!</missionmessage0.tsmmission12>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission12>Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission12>
  <missionname.tsmmission13>BUG! BUG!</missionname.tsmmission13>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission13>We have detected a swarm of large worms nearby and expect them to reach this outpost within five hours. Captain, please repel them, or we will all be buried in the ocean.</missiondescription.tsmmission13>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission13>All targets eliminated.</missionsuccess.tsmmission13>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission13>Swarm Terminator</missionheader0.tsmmission13>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission13>We don't fear the worms anymore!</missionmessage0.tsmmission13>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission13>BUG</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission13>
  <missionname.tsmmission14>The Deepest Nightmares</missionname.tsmmission14>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission14>!!! Emergency !!! T.S.M frontline observatory found some giant beasts quickly approaching this area, but the Sundown special-op assault squad is out on a mission, they cannot rush back in time. T.S.M is calling for heroic captains to stop disaster from happening and promising that the captain who can return alive will be rewarded with [reward] mk.</missiondescription.tsmmission14>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission14>We've brought down the gods.</missionsuccess.tsmmission14>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission14>Monsters and Demons</missionheader0.tsmmission14>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission14>It's incredible, you really made it, worthy of a legendary captain!</missionmessage0.tsmmission14>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission14>Nightmares</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission14>
  <missionname.tsmmission15>The storm gathering close, the submarine carried to the clouds</missionname.tsmmission15>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission15>A school of hammerheads is endangering submarines travelling between [location1] and [location2]. They have swept away many outposts and are enthroned as a god in some areas. Captain, please attack and destroy them.</missiondescription.tsmmission15>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission15>I have destroyed Gods.</missionsuccess.tsmmission15>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission15>Not worthy of a fight.</missionheader0.tsmmission15>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission15>Old gods fall, new gods rise.</missionmessage0.tsmmission15>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission15>Storm</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission15>
  <missionname.tsmmission16>Latchers Incoming!</missionname.tsmmission16>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission16>The Sea of Miracles has observed a group of Latchers advancing towards this area. We promise to reward the captain who repels them with [reward]mk.</missiondescription.tsmmission16>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission16>Breaking the latch</missionsuccess.tsmmission16>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission16>The impact not to take place</missionheader0.tsmmission16>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission16>Captain, well done, you have protected this area once again.</missionmessage0.tsmmission16>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission16>Latcher</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission16>
  <missionname.tsmmission17>The lamenting First Creatures</missionname.tsmmission17>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission17>Captain, we have found in this area multiple crawler clans fighting for territory. They are interfering with inter-outpost navigation, so we sent down a squad to deal with them, but the contact was lost quickly. It's an emergency, so we decided to hire you to find the whereabouts of the lost soldiers and annihilate the threats - every one of them.</missiondescription.tsmmission17>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission17>The crawlers' graveyard? No, our graveyard.</missionsuccess.tsmmission17>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission17>The dissolved past</missionheader0.tsmmission17>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission17>We found our warriors in uniforms of The Sea of Miracles inside the stomachs of the crawlers. So young they were, yet they received treatment like soldiers, deployment like weapons, and burial like objects. In the end, they received no honor or praise which they deserved, or even a decent funeral.</missionmessage0.tsmmission17>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission17>Crawler</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission17>
  <missionname.tsmmission21>Test Subjects of Europa Magic and Biology Inc.</missionname.tsmmission21>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission21>The Europa Magic and Biology Inc. has donated a batch of modified mysterious creatures to East Asia Heavy Industries. However, during testing, the subjects escaped. We have previously sent the Sundown Forces to suppress them, but the contact was lost immediately they encountered the subjects. Be aware, captain, these are not ordinary spinelings, so please handle them carefully.</missiondescription.tsmmission21>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission21>This mission must be kept confidential, or East Asia Heavy Industries will face heavy fines.</missionsuccess.tsmmission21>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission21>Containment Failure</missionheader0.tsmmission21>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission21>Hush! Silence!</missionmessage0.tsmmission21>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission21>Subject 001</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission21>
  <missionname.tsmmission23>EMBI Proving Grounds</missionname.tsmmission23>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission23>The Europa Magic and Biology Inc. has issued a challenge. Their new test subjects are ready for use and they are recruiting captains undaunted by death to record and analyze the subjects' capabilities. If you make it back alive and triumphant, they will offer a generous reward.</missiondescription.tsmmission23>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission23>“The gods are mourning! Let me hear... who is wailing...”</missionsuccess.tsmmission23>
  <missionfailure.tsmmission23>You didn't finish the experiment...</missionfailure.tsmmission23>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission23>The Death Knell</missionheader0.tsmmission23>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission23>The knell rings, but it is a salute to the opening of another world gate.</missionmessage0.tsmmission23>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission23>The Triumvirate</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission23>
  <missionname.tsmmission24>A Broken Star, a Solitary Flame</missionname.tsmmission24>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission24>EMBI has modified Subject T-044 based on data collected from the last combat and is currently recruiting crew members for the challenge. I wonder if you are interested.</missiondescription.tsmmission24>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission24>"The cry of the inferno echoes in the abyss, its angry roar resonating, the sharp whistling sound from its mouthparts filling the waters. The flames it spewed are still burning, and will keep burning...”</missionsuccess.tsmmission24>
  <missionfailure.tsmmission24>You didn't finish the experiment...</missionfailure.tsmmission24>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission24>Mark of the Dead</missionheader0.tsmmission24>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission24>In the abyss, the inferno mourns, I am clad in armor, all were just a few sparks.</missionmessage0.tsmmission24>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission24>T-044-γ</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission24>
  <missionname.tsmmission25>Stump Wood, Feeble Torch</missionname.tsmmission25>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission25>EMBI has modified Subject 009 based on data collected from the last combat and is currently recruiting crew members for the challenge. I wonder if you are interested.</missiondescription.tsmmission25>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission25>"The poisonous fangs of Subject 009 have been pulled out. The decaying torch wanders in the abyss, corpses lay between layers of ice, but do not feel afraid, for our iron beast is blessing us."</missionsuccess.tsmmission25>
  <missionfailure.tsmmission25>You didn't finish the experiment...</missionfailure.tsmmission25>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission25>A Realization that Never Fades</missionheader0.tsmmission25>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission25>In the ice, the plague sweeps, I hold my gun, there was nothing more than the ordinary.</missionmessage0.tsmmission25>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission25>Subject 009</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission25>
  <missionname.tsmmission26>Minions of Memory</missionname.tsmmission26>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission26>EMBI has modified Subject T-037 based on data collected from the last combat and is currently recruiting crew members for the challenge. I wonder if you are interested.</missiondescription.tsmmission26>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission26>"I will present to you my creation that surpasses the gods'."</missionsuccess.tsmmission26>
  <missionfailure.tsmmission26>You didn't finish the experiment...</missionfailure.tsmmission26>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission26>Darkness of the Abyss</missionheader0.tsmmission26>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission26>In Europa, the thunder roars, our machine advances, and the defense line stands.</missionmessage0.tsmmission26>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission26>T-037-α</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission26>
  <missionname.tsmmission31>Mudraptor hunting</missionname.tsmmission31>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission31>While passing through this outpost, we heard that a group of mutated mudraptors are wantonly attacking submarines around. As travelling warriors, we must lend our help.</missiondescription.tsmmission31>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission31>Friend</missionsuccess.tsmmission31>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission31>Helping others is helping yourselves.</missionheader0.tsmmission31>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission31>We come from all corners of the world and go to all ends of it.</missionmessage0.tsmmission31>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission31>Nightmare deathraptor</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission31>
  <missionname.tsmmission32>The Everlasting Past</missionname.tsmmission32>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission32>We found fractal guardians in a cave, apparently still executing their last task - clearing the cave. The minerals in this cave are exactly what this outpost needs. The Sea of Miracles would have ignored this, but they paid us too much. So, what do you choose?</missiondescription.tsmmission32>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission32>This is a story of one forsaken people destroying another.</missionsuccess.tsmmission32>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission32>When this war ends</missionheader0.tsmmission32>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission32>If I ever get a chance to leave Europa like whoever created these machines, I want to see the sunset and feel the seasons. I think she would wish the same.</missionmessage0.tsmmission32>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission32>Fractal Cleaner</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission32>
  <missionname.tsmmission33>Turbulent Waves, Towering Tides</missionname.tsmmission33>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission33>Peace did not last long after we expelled hammerheads from this region. Soon, a new group of native creatures came to occupy this lane. This time, we won't just drive them away: an example is to be made. Eradicate them! We will reward you handsomely.</missiondescription.tsmmission33>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission33>The blood spatters on the hull have not cooled down</missionsuccess.tsmmission33>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission33>More lives are lost at the point of guns</missionheader0.tsmmission33>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission33>We have fought for peace in the area.</missionmessage0.tsmmission33>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission33>Swordhead Shark</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission33>
  <missionname.tsmmission34>Microscopic War</missionname.tsmmission34>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission34>Haha, guess what. We used miniaturizing weapons to shrink some latchers down, but they became too small and escaped the shackles. Captain, take care of them before they cause troubles!</missiondescription.tsmmission34>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission34>An Interesting Experiment</missionsuccess.tsmmission34>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission34>There's no turning back.</missionheader0.tsmmission34>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission34>Hopefully, one day I can have my long-cherished wish realized, cutting off all chains of karma.</missionmessage0.tsmmission34>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission34>Microscopic Latcher</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission34>
  <missionname.tsmmission35>Moloch Surge</missionname.tsmmission35>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission35>We detected a group of anomalous Molochs attacking ships traveling between [location1] and [location2]. Be aware, these Molochs are exceptionally aggresive, please be cautious!</missiondescription.tsmmission35>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission35>The moloch group has been cleared.</missionsuccess.tsmmission35>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission35>The Great Purge Completed</missionheader0.tsmmission35>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission35>All targets neutralized, return to the base!</missionmessage0.tsmmission35>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission35>Moloch</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission35>
  <missionname.tsmmission36>Their Land, Their Blood</missionname.tsmmission36>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission36>Immigrants are flooding into the outpost, making it almost overcrowded. Therefore, we decided to open a new outpost. We scanned a alien ruin in a perfect position, but there are many guardians inside. We hope you can help us with them, the reward will of course not be an issue.</missiondescription.tsmmission36>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission36>"Here intertwines eternity and destruction."</missionsuccess.tsmmission36>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission36>Plunderer</missionheader0.tsmmission36>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission36>We were born plunderers.</missionmessage0.tsmmission36>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission36>Fractal Guardians</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission36>
  <missionname.tsmmission37>Witch Hunt</missionname.tsmmission37>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission37>We located the sub that attacked the "choirs", and it seems to have undergone a secondary mutation. According to information from Vila, this mutated worm seems to be the carrier of previously missing lieutenant, Brynhild. We're unclear about what happened during its disappearance, and no further information was transmitted from Vila yet. But no matter who or what the worm is, it will only cause greater destruction if left alone.</missiondescription.tsmmission37>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission37>The Jaw of the Witch</missionsuccess.tsmmission37>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission37>Eternal Tombstone</missionheader0.tsmmission37>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission37>End</missionmessage0.tsmmission37>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission37>The Witch</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission37>
  <missionname.tsmmission38>Albino Creature</missionname.tsmmission38>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission38>A group of unwelcome guests has arrived in the channel, but it's clear that these creatures are not natural mutants. Alright sailors, it's time to clean up the trash, no matter whose work they are.</missiondescription.tsmmission38>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission38>First Appearance of the Albino Family</missionsuccess.tsmmission38>
  <missionfailure.tsmmission38>Ongoing Death</missionfailure.tsmmission38>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission38>Breaking Dawn</missionheader0.tsmmission38>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission38>I stand in a fusion of water and blood. Above me streak meteors across the sky; below me lay bodies covering the seabed.</missionmessage0.tsmmission38>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission38>Albino Spineling</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission38>
  <missionname.tsmmission41>Earthquake</missionname.tsmmission41>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission41>A massive pulse interference has been detected in the area with severe vibration sensible across the shipping lane. Submarines passing by are advised to steer clear of this lane until The Sea of Miracles resolves the issue.</missiondescription.tsmmission41>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission41>A world-shattering change is upon us.</missionsuccess.tsmmission41>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission41>Judgment</missionheader0.tsmmission41>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission41>I entrust the years to the abyss, letting it undulate beneath my steed. I excavate my own grave in my own eyes.</missionmessage0.tsmmission41>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission41>Epicenter</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission41>
  <missionname.tsmmission42>Whale Surge</missionname.tsmmission42>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission42>There's a profession called whaleman on Earth, and there's also one on Europa, but with different whales. Sailors, proceed to the target area and hunt down the whales there.</missiondescription.tsmmission42>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission42>Doomsday of Whales</missionsuccess.tsmmission42>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission42>Whaleman</missionheader0.tsmmission42>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission42>Congratulations on becoming a qualified whaleman.</missionmessage0.tsmmission42>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission42>Whale</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission42>
  <missionname.tsmmission43>Dreadnought Fleet</missionname.tsmmission43>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission43>A few days ago, the Coalition's Dreadnought Fleet fell in this area. According to gathered information, they are still 'alive.' Our mission now is to ensure their true demise. Be cautious: this operation requires high maneuverability.</missiondescription.tsmmission43>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission43>Hypermobile Warfare</missionsuccess.tsmmission43>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission43>Dreadnought? Deadnought!</missionheader0.tsmmission43>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission43>The true Dreadnought Fleet should rest in the ship graveyard.</missionmessage0.tsmmission43>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission43>Dreadnought</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission43>
  <missionname.tsmmission44>Pretenders</missionname.tsmmission44>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission44>Captain, this is a commission from the mining outpost. It's said that their mining ships were attacked by the mines themselves. I'm not sure how such an absurd statement came about, but please investigate.</missiondescription.tsmmission44>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission44>Mineral Encounter</missionsuccess.tsmmission44>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission44>The Birth of Heresy</missionheader0.tsmmission44>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission44>I feel that our misdeeds will eventually lead to our demise in this foreign land.</missionmessage0.tsmmission44>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission44>"Mine"</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission44>
  <missionname.tsmmission45>Twin Paradox</missionname.tsmmission45>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission45>We discovered two alien constructs driven by the brains of a pair of twins. I don't know how I feel about this kind of brain extraction, but it must have been cruel and inhumane. However, we have no capacity to pity these twins; the only thing we can do is to send them to their deaths and hope they will never reborn on Europa.</missiondescription.tsmmission45>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission45>The Operator, the Rioter, the Originator</missionsuccess.tsmmission45>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission45>It's actually a sad story.</missionheader0.tsmmission45>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission45>Civilization and history weigh heavily on it.</missionmessage0.tsmmission45>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission45>Twin</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission45>
  <missionname.tsmmission46>Ecliptic Shadow</missionname.tsmmission46>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission46>When wings turn into swimming fish, the curtain of invasion falls. They dwell in deep caves, guarding treasures like dragons. Their thunderous blasts resonate. This is their kingdom; entering it means starting a war.</missiondescription.tsmmission46>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission46>The Machine of War</missionsuccess.tsmmission46>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission46>The March of History</missionheader0.tsmmission46>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission46>The victor is not who respects life and harmonic coexistence. When the final strike fell, the last guardians of the cave became nourishment for the sea, leaving nothing behind.</missionmessage0.tsmmission46>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission46>Shadow Raider</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission46>
  <missionname.tsmmission47>Cloud Piercer</missionname.tsmmission47>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission47>Recently, people at the outpost discovered a new species of fish. Its meat is delicious and fetches a good price. However, most of them live in caves. Fishermen here are offering a bounty for someone to enter the caves and drive them out, which would allow for unobstructed fishing.</missiondescription.tsmmission47>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission47>Money is Your Lie</missionsuccess.tsmmission47>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission47>Bloody Massacre</missionheader0.tsmmission47>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission47>A photograph was taken, documenting another achievement of the crew, another great victory of human over nature...</missionmessage0.tsmmission47>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission47>Skypiercing Dolphin</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission47>
  <missionname.tsmmission51>Living Carcass</missionname.tsmmission51>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission51>We lost contact with this outpost a while ago. Before that, a special cargo of eggs was delivered there. We suspect someone deliberately placed them at the outpost. Your mission is to clear everything that still moves at the outpost and destroy the reactor.</missiondescription.tsmmission51>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission51>The outpost has been cleared, leave the follow-up to us.</missionsuccess.tsmmission51>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission51>Tartarus</missionheader0.tsmmission51>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission51>The Sea of Miracles has found information about this cargo, but give us some time to decrypt it. We will find out who is behind this and make them pay.</missionmessage0.tsmmission51>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission51>Unknown Lifeform</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission51>
  <missionname.tsmmission52>Crisis! Sinking of the Choir</missionname.tsmmission52>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission52>Captain, our submarine transporting genes... let me correct my self, our submarine transporting a choir was attacked by an unknown creature and sunk. Please search the area and retrieve important data on the wreck as soon as possible.</missiondescription.tsmmission52>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission52>Retrieval Succeeds</missionsuccess.tsmmission52>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission52>Everyone sinks until they cannot sink anymore.</missionheader0.tsmmission52>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission52>Well done, Captain. The Sea of Miracles will give you further orders as soon as we decrypt the data. What a pity about these choir boys...</missionmessage0.tsmmission52>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission52>Wreck</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission52>
  <missionname.tsmmission53>Concert</missionname.tsmmission53>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission53>The music of death echoes in their ears, souls from the abyss climb into the outpost, nothing reflects from their turbid eyes. I feel like I've slept for a long time, but now I'm finally awake. (Clear all living creatures in the outpost and destroy the reactor)</missiondescription.tsmmission53>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission53>Concerto of Death</missionsuccess.tsmmission53>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission53>Fear of the Unknown</missionheader0.tsmmission53>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission53>There is no longer a soul inside the carcass, but the singing continues, she's still chanting...</missionmessage0.tsmmission53>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission53>The Singer</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission53>
  <missionname.tsmmission60>All in the Name of Justice</missionname.tsmmission60>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission60>The Sea of Miracles has blocked the lane between [location1] and [location2], but you're willing to take the risk...</missiondescription.tsmmission60>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission60>Lives dissipate as blood disappears into water.</missionsuccess.tsmmission60>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission60>The Tomb</missionheader0.tsmmission60>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission60>“Now this is really not worth it...”</missionmessage0.tsmmission60>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission60>HTC24 Turquoise</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission60>
  <missionname.tsmmission54>Quick Reaction Force</missionname.tsmmission54>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission54>An elite squadron of the Coalition attacked and took over this outpost. They may launch a preemtive attack on any docked submarine. Eliminate them and destroy the reactor to claim the Separatists' bounty.</missiondescription.tsmmission54>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission54>Underwater Mist</missionsuccess.tsmmission54>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission54>The Tomb</missionheader0.tsmmission54>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission54>Mission accomplished. Return to the submarine and contact the Separatists to collect your reward.</missionmessage0.tsmmission54>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission54>Quick Reaction Force</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission54>
  <character.Experiment_T044Y>The Inferno</character.Experiment_T044Y>
  <character.荒疫>The Plague</character.荒疫>
  <character.雷龙>The Thunder</character.雷龙>
  <character.T037α>Subject T-037-α</character.T037α>
  <character.T044Y>Subject T-044-γ</character.T044Y>
  <character.Experiment009>Subject 009</character.Experiment009>
  <character.巨型女妖>Giant Charybdis</character.巨型女妖>
  <character.微观捕勾兽>Microscopic Latcher</character.微观捕勾兽>
  <character.微观捕勾兽模板>Microscopic Latcher</character.微观捕勾兽模板>
  <character.NightmareMudraptor>Nightmare Mudraptor</character.NightmareMudraptor>
  <character.FractalTwin_Destruction>Destruction</character.FractalTwin_Destruction>
  <character.FractalTwin_Sabotage>Sabotage</character.FractalTwin_Sabotage>
  <character.Shadowreave>Shadow Reave</character.Shadowreave>
  <character.Eclipticshadow>Shadowreave</character.Eclipticshadow>
  <character.Skypiercingdolphin>Skypiercing Dolphin</character.Skypiercingdolphin>
  <character.Shadowcharm>Shadowcharm</character.Shadowcharm>
  <character.AlbinismSpineling_giant>Albino Spineling</character.AlbinismSpineling_giant>
  <character.AlbinismSpineling>Albino Spineling</character.AlbinismSpineling>
  <character.corruptionMachinery>Corrupt Machinery</character.corruptionMachinery>
  <character.OceanEnchantress>Ocean Enchantress</character.OceanEnchantress>
  <character.zhaoge>Zhaoge</character.zhaoge>
  <character.corrode>Corrosion</character.corrode>
  <character.MobileTaskForce>TSM Mobile Task Force</character.MobileTaskForce>
  <character.MobileTaskForce1>TSM Mobile Task Force</character.MobileTaskForce1>
  <character.RiotSquad>TSM Mobile Task Force</character.RiotSquad>
  <character.sundownm>Sundown Forces</character.sundownm>
  <character.Ship>HTC24 Turquoise Troop Carrier</character.Ship>
  <character.Ship1>HTC24 Turquoise</character.Ship1>
  <character.Ship2>HTC24 Turquoise</character.Ship2>
  <character.Ship3>HTC24 Turquoise</character.Ship3>
  <character.sight>Landing Craft</character.sight>
  <character.sight1>Landing Craft</character.sight1>
  <character.sight2>Landing Craft</character.sight2>
  <character.sight3>Landing Craft</character.sight3>
  <character.UnionRiotRaiders>Coalition Riot Commando</character.UnionRiotRaiders>
  <character.UnionRiotAttacker>Coalition Riot Attacker</character.UnionRiotAttacker>
  <character.QuickReactionForce>Coalition Riot Quick Reaction Force</character.QuickReactionForce>
  <character.QuickReactionForce1>Coalition Riot Quick Reaction Force</character.QuickReactionForce1>
  <tsm.a1>Hello, I am the captain of Peregrine Falcon Squad, The Sea of Miracles. We're overwhelmed with tasks and can't handle everything, so we're hoping for some assistance with certain matters, and of course, we'll pay for it!</tsm.a1>
  <tsm.a2>The situation in The Sea of Miracles is not great. We were about to head to Kyushu Armory, but then commissions came up here. What's your opinion about finishing them for us? </tsm.a2>
  <tsm.a3>Hello, I am the liaison officer from EMBI. We have posted a few commissions; are you interested in any of them?</tsm.a3>
  <tsm.a4>Europa is vast, we love it in its immensity; time is long, we love it in its brevity; our lives are eager and fiery, deserving of living slowly, and also deserving of sudden death. This is a world where departure is common, but sadly, we're not good at goodbyes. Thus, before setting sail, the most important thing is to first be brave, then honest, and finally, believe in the existence of miracles! And, never forget each other...</tsm.a4>
  <tsm.a4>I still have precious memories of Earth in my mind. The azure sky with gleaming stars, how beautiful the world was...</tsm.a4>
  <tsm.a4>What is more important than wealth and glory in Europa is trust. Sailor, can I trust you?</tsm.a4>
  <tsm.a4>Hi sailor, have you seen captain Eagle recently? No, I'm just asking. I think I left a toy duck in his locker before I realized it was stuffed with UEX...</tsm.a4>
  <tsm.a4>Human beings are distinguished from animals because they have not only animal instincts but also free will and absolute spirituality. Do you want to live like a human or an animal, sailor?</tsm.a4>
  <tsm.a5>What? You say you want to buy some slaves for your ship? Sorry, this is no longer a slave market. Slavery has been banned, so now we call it a talent market.</tsm.a5>
  <tsm.a5>The 'summer' I spent with them was cruel indeed, so many people I'll never see again...</tsm.a5>
  <tsm.a5>What paranormal event? Don't give me that nonsense about ghosts and goblins; the engine's tail flame can melt all ignorance and superstition.</tsm.a5>
  <tsm.a5>We are now walking the path our predecessors have trodden. For them in another dimension, these are history, but for us, they are experiences.</tsm.a5>
  <tsm.a6>Don't negate all the meetings and companionships just because everything ends in death and departure.</tsm.a6>
  <tsm.a7>Hello I Kuiteman, I've sent the recent commissions to your terminal, thanks for your cooperation.</tsm.a7>
  <tsm.a71>I guess you are kuiteman pig!</tsm.a71>
  <tsm.a72>O.o</tsm.a72>
  <tsm.a8>Hey, dude, welcome to our outpost. We've been having some trouble lately, can I ask you a favor?</tsm.a8>
  <tsm.a81>Though he wears a clown mask, his flamboyant attire allows you to instantly recognize him as a bishop wanted by both the Coalition and TSM. Looking around, you decided to listen to what kind of favor he's going to ask.</tsm.a81>
  <tsm.a82>I was heading to the next outpost, but the channel is blocked by The Sea of Miracles right now. I have something very important to do there, if... I mean, if you could help deal with them...</tsm.a82>
  <tsm.a83>It would depend on how sincere you'd like to be.</tsm.a83>
  <tsm.a84>Oh! My friend, I can be as sincere as you want me to be.</tsm.a84>
  <tsm.a8a>You recognize him as a wanted man and handcuff him.</tsm.a8a>
  <tsm.a8b>"You asshole, do you know where you are! This is not the territory of your The Seditionists of Mendacity! Somebody, somebody!" The bishop yells over, and everyone around you leans toward you with all kinds of weapons.</tsm.a8b>
  <tsm.a8c>You have a bad feeling and are about to flee when an explosion goes off and the Coalition Riot Suppression Force invades from all over the place.</tsm.a8c>
  <tsm.a8d>While you're still in a daze, you hear from a walkie-talkie, "Empty the room, leave no one alive!"</tsm.a8d>
  <tsm.b8>Ignore him and leave.</tsm.b8>
  <tsm.lq>Getting the job done</tsm.lq>
  <tsm.dh>redemption item</tsm.dh>
  <tsm.see>I'd better take another look.</tsm.see>
  <tsm.wait>Come back later.</tsm.wait>
  <tsm.wait1>Let me wait a little longer.</tsm.wait1>
  <tsm.next>Welcome to the next one.</tsm.next>
  <tsm.next1>Sorry about that, the price is still a bit high for you, come back next time.</tsm.next1>
  <tsm.next2>You don't have enough money, should you take on some tasks to earn money?</tsm.next2>
  <tsm.zssd>50 MK for tactical flashlight</tsm.zssd>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_1>Lang</charactername.TSMnpc_1>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_2>Youmu</charactername.TSMnpc_2>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_3>EMBI Liaison Officer</charactername.TSMnpc_3>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_4>Tom Suger</charactername.TSMnpc_4>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_5>Lerentine</charactername.TSMnpc_5>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_6>Qijiang</charactername.TSMnpc_6>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_7>Kuiteman</charactername.TSMnpc_7>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_8>The Bishop</charactername.TSMnpc_8>
  <entityname.mvdxe>Witch's Jaw</entityname.mvdxe>
  <entitydescription.mvdxe>A proof of your victory over her.</entitydescription.mvdxe>
  <entityname.lldyj>T037's Eye</entityname.lldyj>
  <entitydescription.lldyj>A proof of your victory over her.</entitydescription.lldyj>
  <entityname.hyddx>009's Poison Gland</entityname.hyddx>
  <entitydescription.hyddx>A proof of your victory over her.</entitydescription.hyddx>
  <entityname.ddbm>T044's Organ</entityname.ddbm>
  <entitydescription.ddbm>A proof of your victory over her.</entitydescription.ddbm>
  <entityname.AlbinismSpineling>Albino Spineling's Spike</entityname.AlbinismSpineling>
  <entitydescription.AlbinismSpineling>Can be used to construct railgun shells or deconstructed into steel.</entitydescription.AlbinismSpineling>
  <entityname.tsm_soundplayer>Music Player</entityname.tsm_soundplayer>
  <entitydescription.tsm_soundplayer>Plays audio tapes obtained from creatures or purchased at outposts.</entitydescription.tsm_soundplayer>
  <entityname.Extra_hat_male_tsm>Chief Officer's Hat</entityname.Extra_hat_male_tsm>
  <entitydescription.Extra_hat_male_tsm>The last piece of conscience, the last balance of order</entitydescription.Extra_hat_male_tsm>
  <entityname.suger_boardingaxe>‖color:159,207,217,255‖'Suger's Battle Axe'‖color:end‖</entityname.suger_boardingaxe>
  <entitydescription.suger_boardingaxe>‖color:159,207,217,255‖Swing towards the enemy, and also towards one's former self.‖color:end‖</entitydescription.suger_boardingaxe>
  <entityname.tsm_tcr_missions>‖color:210,110,0,255‖'Chariots' Assault Rifle‖color:end‖</entityname.tsm_tcr_missions>
  <entitydescription.tsm_tcr_missions>‖color:210,110,0,255‖A flower to the fallen.‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_tcr_missions>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_fymagazine>‖color:55,45,155,255‖'Raven' Rifle‖color:end‖</entityname.tsmmissions_fymagazine>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_fymagazine>‖color:55,45,155,255‖A variable, an opportunity.‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsmmissions_fymagazine>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_Icarus>‖color:159,207,217,255‖Hand Cannon Icarus‖color:end‖</entityname.tsmmissions_Icarus>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_Icarus>‖color:159,207,217,255‖Suger's sidearm, a rotary pistol with integrated flashlight and grenade launcher, fires regular handcannon rounds. It was gifted by Commander Lerentine when Suger joined TSM, and has remained reliable through battles large and small. No one knows how a man of Suger's stature can single-handedly operate a pistol of this horrendously large caliber.\n\n“In mid-air, the wax of hypocrisy melted under the sun, and Icarus crashed into the sea”‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsmmissions_Icarus>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_lrmagazine>'Raven' Magazine</entityname.tsmmissions_lrmagazine>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_lrmagazine />
  <entityname.tsmmissions_magazine_bg>'Chariots' Special Cartridge</entityname.tsmmissions_magazine_bg>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_magazine_bg />
  <entityname.tsmmissions_magazine_kr>'Chariots' Expanded Magazine</entityname.tsmmissions_magazine_kr>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_magazine_kr />
  <entityname.tsmmissions_TTI2011>‖color:100,0,0,255‖TTI2011‖color:end‖</entityname.tsmmissions_TTI2011>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_TTI2011>‖color:100,0,0,255‖The only heirloom left by Father.‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsmmissions_TTI2011>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_TTI2011ammo>TTI2011 Magazine</entityname.tsmmissions_TTI2011ammo>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_TTI2011ammo />
  <entityname.AlbinismSpineling_shell>Albino Spineling Canister Shell</entityname.AlbinismSpineling_shell>
  <entitydescription.AlbinismSpineling_shell>Can be reloaded.</entitydescription.AlbinismSpineling_shell>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_flashlight>Tactical Flashlight</entityname.tsmmissions_flashlight>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_flashlight>Flashlight, but better.</entitydescription.tsmmissions_flashlight>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_laser>Laser Pointer</entityname.tsmmissions_laser>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_laser />
  <entityname.tsm_advancedcomsuit>Military Advanced Protective Suit</entityname.tsm_advancedcomsuit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advancedcomsuit>Low-oxygen alarm was damaged in combat.</entitydescription.tsm_advancedcomsuit>
  <entityname.tsm_riotcontrolsuit>Riot Control Suit</entityname.tsm_riotcontrolsuit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_riotcontrolsuit>Low-oxygen alarm was damaged in combat.</entitydescription.tsm_riotcontrolsuit>
  <entityname.tsm_hdlcsuits>Heavy-Duty Cast Lead Diving Suit</entityname.tsm_hdlcsuits>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hdlcsuits>Low-oxygen alarm was damaged in combat.</entitydescription.tsm_hdlcsuits>
  <entityname.tsm_advancedcombat_helmet_thermalgoggles>Advanced Combat Helmet (Thermal Imaging)</entityname.tsm_advancedcombat_helmet_thermalgoggles>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advancedcombat_helmet_thermalgoggles />
  <entityname.tsm_advancedcombat_helmet_mask>Advanced Combat Helmet (Riot Mask)</entityname.tsm_advancedcombat_helmet_mask>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advancedcombat_helmet_mask />
  <entityname.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_helmet>Coalition Contingent Helmet</entityname.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_helmet>
  <entitydescription.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_helmet />
  <entityname.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_vest>Coalition Contingent Body Armor</entityname.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_vest />
  <entityname.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_uniform>Coalition Contingent Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_Coalitioncontingents_uniform />
  <entityname.tsm_old>Old Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_old>
  <entitydescription.tsm_old />
  <entityname.tsm_orangeconstant_o1>Damaged Orange-Volatile Suit</entityname.tsm_orangeconstant_o1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant_o1>This suit was damaged in combat, with many functions disabled.</entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant_o1>
  <entityname.tsm_orangeconstant_o2>Damaged Orange-Volatile Suit</entityname.tsm_orangeconstant_o2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant_o1>This suit was damaged in combat, with many functions disabled.</entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant_o1>
  <entityname.tsm_orangeconstant_o3>Damaged Orange-Volatile Suit</entityname.tsm_orangeconstant_o3>
  <entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant_o3>This suit was damaged in combat, with many functions disabled.</entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant_o3>
  <subcategory.tsmmissions>T.S.M. MISSIONS - The Sea of Miracles</subcategory.tsmmissions>
  <missionname.tsmmission1>The Watch of T.S.M</missionname.tsmmission1>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission1>T.S.M is fighting against the Beast at frontline position in Area 73 of The Aphotic Plateau and currently has no time left to protect the area, but the Beast is approaching and T.S.M promises a [reward] mk to anyone who kills the beast.</missiondescription.tsmmission1>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission1>Target confirmed and terminated.</missionsuccess.tsmmission1>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission1>People expect good news from you</missionheader0.tsmmission1>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission1>T.S.M is looking forward to collaborating with you next time.</missionmessage0.tsmmission1>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission1>target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission1>
  <missionname.tsmmission2>Eclipse</missionname.tsmmission2>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission2>T.S.M is fighting in frontline Area 73 and has no time to worry about the safety of this area, but T.S.M guarantees a [reward] mk to the captain who kills these beasts.</missiondescription.tsmmission2>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission2>Congratulations, you made it!</missionsuccess.tsmmission2>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission2>Third Contact of Eclipse</missionheader0.tsmmission2>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission2>What a bright performance!</missionmessage0.tsmmission2>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission2>target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission2>
  <missionname.tsmmission3>The Deepest Nightmares</missionname.tsmmission3>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission3>!!! Emergency !!! T.S.M frontline observatory found some giant beasts quickly approaching this area, but the Sundown special-op assault squad is out on a mission, they cannot rush back in time. T.S.M is calling for heroic captains to stop disaster from happening and promising that the captain who can return alive will be rewarded with [reward] mk.</missiondescription.tsmmission3>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission3>We've brought down the gods.</missionsuccess.tsmmission3>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission3>The Deepest Nightmares</missionheader0.tsmmission3>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission3>It's incredible, you really made it, worthy of a legendary captain!</missionmessage0.tsmmission3>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission3>Nightmares</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission3>
  <missionname.tsmmission4>Here comes Latcher~</missionname.tsmmission4>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission4>T.S.M observed a group of Latchers coming towards this area, and we promised a reward of [reward] mk to the captain who repelled them.</missiondescription.tsmmission4>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission4>We break the latch.</missionsuccess.tsmmission4>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission4>Shocks that did not occur</missionheader0.tsmmission4>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission4>Well done, you have defended the area once again, captain.</missionmessage0.tsmmission4>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission4>Latcher</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission4>
  <missionname.tsmmission5>EMBI Experimental Biology Body</missionname.tsmmission5>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission5>Europa Magic Biotechnology Inc.(EMBI) donated a batch of modified mystical creatures to East Asia-Heavy Industry (EA-HI) , but EA-HI failed to contain them during testing, we had previously sent Sundown special-op assault squad over to suppress them, but lost the message after contact with the experiments, please be advised Captain, this is not ordinary bunch of giant spinelings! Please be very careful!</missiondescription.tsmmission5>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission5>This mission must be kept secret or the EA-HI will face a hefty fine.</missionsuccess.tsmmission5>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission5>Containment Breach</missionheader0.tsmmission5>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission5>Shh! Silence, please!</missionmessage0.tsmmission5>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission5>Experiment.1</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission5>
  <missionname.tsmmission6>Moloch Wave</missionname.tsmmission6>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission6>We have heard a swarm of Moloch attacking traveling ships between [location1] and [location2]. This area is not under the jurisdiction of T.S.M, but for humanitarian reasons we promise to give [reward]mk to the captain that clears this bunch of creatures.</missiondescription.tsmmission6>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission6>The Moloch swarm has been eradicated.</missionsuccess.tsmmission6>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission6>Great purge completed.</missionheader0.tsmmission6>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission6>All monsters have been eliminated,navigate back now.</missionmessage0.tsmmission6>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission6>Moloch</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission6>
  <missionname.tsmmission7>Storms converge, lift me to the clouds</missionname.tsmmission7>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission7>A large bunch of Hammerheads have threatened the safety of the passage between [location1] and [location2]. This Hammerhead sharknado has swept through many stations, and some people in the area have already been worshipping them as gods. So please, Captain, fire out and destroy them!</missiondescription.tsmmission7>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission7>Their altars are erased by me.</missionsuccess.tsmmission7>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission7>cannot withstand a single blow</missionheader0.tsmmission7>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission7>The fall of the old gods, the rise of the new ones.</missionmessage0.tsmmission7>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission7>Storms</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission7>
  <missionname.tsmmission8>Worm‘s World Party</missionname.tsmmission8>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission8>We have detected several large worms approaching the area and expecting to reach this station in 5 hours, Captain please repel them or we will all be buried in the cold currents.</missiondescription.tsmmission8>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission8>Target down, please return to the station ASAP.</missionsuccess.tsmmission8>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission8>Worm Terminator</missionheader0.tsmmission8>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission8>We are no longer afraid of the worms!</missionmessage0.tsmmission8>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission8>Worms</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission8>
  <missionname.tsmmission9>Endwhale Wave</missionname.tsmmission9>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission9>Did you know that there is a profession called 'whaler' back on Earth, and there is also such a profession in Europa, but the whale is absolutely different. Well sailor, head to the target area and eradicate all cetacean creatures.</missiondescription.tsmmission9>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission9>The End for Endwhale.</missionsuccess.tsmmission9>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission9>Whaler</missionheader0.tsmmission9>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission9>Congratulations, you have become a certified whaler!</missionmessage0.tsmmission9>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission9>Endwhale</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission9>
  <missionname.tsmmission10>Dreadnought Fleet</missionname.tsmmission10>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission10>Not long ago, a Coalition dreadnought fleet fell in the region, but according to the information gathered, they are still 'alive', now the task is to ensure that they are really dead. Please note that it better be a ultra-mobile operation.</missiondescription.tsmmission10>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission10>Now that's called ultra-mobile operation.</missionsuccess.tsmmission10>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission10>Dreadnought? Deadnought!</missionheader0.tsmmission10>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission10>The real dreadnought fleet should sink in the ship cemetry.</missionmessage0.tsmmission10>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission10>Dreadnought</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission10>
  <missionname.tsmmission18>The Living Dead</missionname.tsmmission18>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission18>This station suddenly lost contact some time ago. Before that there had been a special shipment to this station, investigation shows it was some special eggs, so your task is to clean up this station of all living things and clean up all the eggs.</missiondescription.tsmmission18>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission18>The station has been cleared, leave the follow-up to T.S.M.</missionsuccess.tsmmission18>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission18>Tartarus</missionheader0.tsmmission18>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission18>T.S.M found the information of this shipment, but please give us some time to decrypt the data and we will find the person behind this.</missionmessage0.tsmmission18>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission18>Unknown Life Form</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission18>
  <missionname.tsmmission19>Raging Waves</missionname.tsmmission19>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission19>We drove away the hammerheads some time ago, but the area has not been peaceful for long, soon a new group of natives continue to dominate this channel, so this time we can not just drive them away, but to make them an example for others. I have to remind you may need to prepare some more anaparalyzant and calyxanide. Destroy this group of natives! We will give you a generous reward.</missiondescription.tsmmission19>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission19>Blood on our hands is not yet cold.</missionsuccess.tsmmission19>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission19>Another soul perished because of us.</missionheader0.tsmmission19>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission19>This channel will finally be peaceful for a while.</missionmessage0.tsmmission19>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission19>Swordhead Shark Swarm</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission19>
  <missionname.tsmmission20>EMBI Experiments 1</missionname.tsmmission20>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission20>Europa Magic Biotechnology Inc.(EMBI) has issued a challenge, their new experimental subject is ready for use and they are recruiting brave crew members to test the strength of the new subject, then they will record the data during the battle. If someone survived to come back, they will provide a generous bonus.</missiondescription.tsmmission20>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission20>"Gods are mourning! Let me hear... Who is crying----"</missionsuccess.tsmmission20>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission20>Death knell</missionheader0.tsmmission20>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission20>The death knell had been rung, it's a salute to the opening door to another world.</missionmessage0.tsmmission20>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission20>New Experimental Subjects</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission20>
  <missionname.tsmmission22>Micro Warfare</missionname.tsmmission22>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission22>Hey, hey, guess what. We used a micro weapon to shrink some latcher, and since they got too small, they all got away, so the captain has to get to them quickly!</missiondescription.tsmmission22>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission22>Interesting experiments</missionsuccess.tsmmission22>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission22>No turning back</missionheader0.tsmmission22>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission22>Will we tire of slaying endless beasts that hunt them</missionmessage0.tsmmission22>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission22>Small latcher</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission22>
  <laser>Laser Pointer</laser>
  <entityname.tsm-mvdxe>DRK-11</entityname.tsm-mvdxe>
  <missionname.tsmattack>Night Ambush</missionname.tsmattack>
  <missionheader0.tsmattack>Begin operation, engagement rule: Kill on sight</missionheader0.tsmattack>
  <missionmessage0.tsmattack>This world is not short of death</missionmessage0.tsmattack>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin1>Bounty Mission: Hunt the Doomworm</missionname.tsmmission_origin1>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin1>There is a Doomworm harassing our transport between [location1] and [location2]. This time, someone has offered a bounty of [reward]mk. The mission target is to kill this worm.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin1>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin1>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin1>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin1>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin1>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin1>Congratulations on completing the mission, the bounty reward will be sent to your account after you reach the next station.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin1>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin1>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin1>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin2>Bounty Mission: Hunt the Banshee</missionname.tsmmission_origin2>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin2>A Banshee has made its home in the passage between [location1] and [location2], constantly harassing nearby stations and passing ships. We are offering a bounty of [reward]mk for its head.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin2>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin2>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin2>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin2>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin2>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin2>Congratulations on completing the mission, the money will be sent to your account after you reach the next station.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin2>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin2>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin2>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin3>Bounty Mission: Hunt the Hook Beast</missionname.tsmmission_origin3>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin3>A foreign Hook Beast has taken over the abyss in this passage, making our abyss mining operations difficult. We promise a reward of [reward]mk to anyone who kills this Hook Beast.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin3>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin3>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin3>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin3>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin3>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin3>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin3>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin3>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin3>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin4>Bounty Mission: Hunt the Cyber Worm</missionname.tsmmission_origin4>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin4>Our abyss exploration team detected sonar signals similar to a Cyber Worm during their operation, so they issued a bounty of [reward]mk to kill this Cyber Worm and ensure the safety of the abyss exploration.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin4>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin4>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin4>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin4>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin4>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin4>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. We will continue exploring the abyss.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin4>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin4>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin4>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin5>Bounty Mission: Hunt the Giant Spine Cluster</missionname.tsmmission_origin5>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin5>Ships frequently went missing in the passage, and after investigating the cause, it was found that a group of giant spines from other seas had settled in. This poses a serious threat to the safety of our passage, so the target this time is this group of spines.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin5>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin5>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin5>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin5>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin5>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin5>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. The passage has returned to calm.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin5>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin5>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin5>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin6>Bounty Mission: Hunt the Venomous Serpent Cluster</missionname.tsmmission_origin6>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin6>Our hospital suddenly received a batch of patients who were suffocated and poisoned. According to the rescued crew members, they were attacked by venomous serpents during their voyage. For everyone's safety, these venomous serpents must die.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin6>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin6>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin6>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin6>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin6>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin6>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. We won't suffer from suffocation poisoning again.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin6>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin6>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin6>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin7>Bounty Mission: Raptor Ambush</missionname.tsmmission_origin7>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin7>A large number of raptors have taken over what was once a safe passage, threatening the safety of nearby stations. We are offering a bounty of [reward]mk to recruit a fleet to ambush these raptors.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin7>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin7>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin7>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin7>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin7>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin7>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. The ambush was perfectly executed.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin7>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin7>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin7>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin8>Bounty Mission: Black Moloch Extermination</missionname.tsmmission_origin8>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin8>Some clueless crew killed a few baby Molochs while passing through the passage between [location1] and [location2]. Now a group of Black Molochs has taken over the passage, and we have no choice but to summon brave warriors to help clear the situation.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin8>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin8>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin8>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin8>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin8>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin8>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. The Black Molochs have been exterminated.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin8>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin8>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin8>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin9>Bounty Mission: Thresher Group Extermination</missionname.tsmmission_origin9>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin9>A group of Tiger Threshers have occupied the passage, attacking nearby stations and destroying passing ships. Several brave warriors have gone to eliminate them, but none returned. The fleet that successfully wipes out this group and returns safely can claim the reward at the next station.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin9>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin9>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin9>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin9>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin9>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin9>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. The Tiger Threshers could not escape extermination.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin9>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin9>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin9>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin10>Bounty Mission: Invitation of the Aliens</missionname.tsmmission_origin10>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin10>A relic exploration team accidentally released several guards while exploring a ruin. These guards caused a serious safety incident, so we need someone to clean up the mess.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin10>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin10>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin10>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin10>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin10>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin10>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. Technically, we are the aliens here.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin10>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin10>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin10>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin11>Bounty Mission: Barbarians in the Cave</missionname.tsmmission_origin11>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin11>This bounty was issued by the Husk Cult. Some radical members, after taking special Husk eggs, robbed the cult's Husk boxes and fled to a cave. The cult hopes someone can help clean house and destroy those Husk boxes.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin11>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin11>Mission Complete</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin11>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin11>Hunt Finished</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin11>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin11>Congratulations on completing the mission, [reward]mk will be sent to your account after you reach the next station. Those strong bodies and low intelligence — was it ascension or failure?</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin11>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin11>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin11>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin13>Transport Decaying Material</missionname.tsmmission_origin13>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin13>A few boxes of decaying material urgently need to be transported to [location2]. Attention! You only have ten minutes.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin13>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin13>Express Delivery</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin13>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin13>Express Delivery</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin13>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin13>Racing with Death</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin13>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin14>Transport Leather Materials</missionname.tsmmission_origin14>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin14>A wealthy individual at [location2] has ordered some high-quality leather. This leather is very precious and cannot come into contact with water, or it will be ruined. So, be very careful during transport.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin14>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin14>Task completed with quality and quantity</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin14>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin14>The best delivery service</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin14>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin14>Task completed with quality and quantity</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin14>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin15>Transport Captured Adventist Members</missionname.tsmmission_origin15>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin15>A few members of the Adventist were arrested at the Sea of Miracles. They now need to be transported to the next station for interrogation.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin15>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin15>No member was left behind</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin15>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin15>Mission Complete</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin15>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin15>No member was left behind</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin15>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin16>Shirok’s Treasure</missionname.tsmmission_origin16>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin16>A mysterious person has entrusted us to transport a package to another mysterious person. He hinted that the package contains Shirok's Treasure (rumor has it, Shirok’s Treasure could break down into anything, but it’s all up to luck).</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin16>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin16>Honesty above all</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin16>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin16>Mission Complete</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin16>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin16>Honesty above all</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin16>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin17>Transport Materials</missionname.tsmmission_origin17>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin17>The Sea of Miracles has entrusted us to transport a batch of raw ore materials.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin17>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin17>Honesty above all</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin17>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin17>Mission Complete</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin17>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin17>Honesty above all</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin17>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin18>Transport Medical Supplies</missionname.tsmmission_origin18>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin18>[location2] is in desperate need of medical supplies. They have ordered a batch from the Sea of Miracles, and it urgently needs to be delivered.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin18>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin18>Honesty above all</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin18>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin18>Mission Complete</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin18>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin18>Honesty above all</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin18>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin19>Transport Sea of Miracles Soldiers</missionname.tsmmission_origin19>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin19>A squad from the Sea of Miracles wishes to travel on your ship to the next station.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin19>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin19>Arrived safely</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin19>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin19>Mission Complete</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin19>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin19>Arrived safely</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin19>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin20>Bounty Mission: Crawler Extermination</missionname.tsmmission_origin20>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin20>A large group of Crawlers is present in the passage. We’ve tried multiple times to drive them away, but with little effect. They aren’t even afraid of station security forces anymore, which means these are no ordinary Crawlers. We need to strike hard.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin20>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin20>The Crawlers are pushing the submarine pilots and training the crew’s shooting skills, what a hassle.</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin20>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin20>Mission Complete</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin20>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin20>The Crawlers are pushing the submarine pilots and training the crew’s shooting skills, what a hassle.</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin20>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin20>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin20>
  <missionname.tsmmission_origin21>Bounty Mission: Farewell, Doomworm</missionname.tsmmission_origin21>
  <missiondescription.tsmmission_origin21>The Doomworm, dormant in the abyss, has become active again. Nearby stations have issued emergency alerts, causing widespread panic. Someone has offered [reward]mk to kill the Doomworm.</missiondescription.tsmmission_origin21>
  <missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin21>Hopefully, it won’t awaken again</missionsuccess.tsmmission_origin21>
  <missionheader0.tsmmission_origin21>Mission Complete</missionheader0.tsmmission_origin21>
  <missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin21>Back to sleep again</missionmessage0.tsmmission_origin21>
  <missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin21>Bounty Target</missionsonarlabel.tsmmission_origin21>
  <character.embi_009>Experiment 009: Plague</character.embi_009>
  <character.embi_t037a>T-037A: Thunder Dragon</character.embi_t037a>
  <character.embi_001>Experiment 001</character.embi_001>
  <character.embi_003>Experiment 003</character.embi_003>
  <character.Experiment009_bug>Toxic Exploder</character.Experiment009_bug>
  <character.tsm_husk_pucs>Living Cadaver</character.tsm_husk_pucs>
  <character.tsm_husk_arm>Living Cadaver</character.tsm_husk_arm>
  <character.tsm_beast>Behemoth</character.tsm_beast>
  <character.tsm_portalguardian_cave>Cave Cleaner</character.tsm_portalguardian_cave>
  <character.tsm_Guardianrepairbot>Repairer</character.tsm_Guardianrepairbot>
  <character.boneeater>Bone Eater</character.boneeater>
  <character.humaneyi>Plague Body</character.humaneyi>
  <character.eyivariant>Mutant</character.eyivariant>
  <character.tsm_tyrant>Tyrant</character.tsm_tyrant>
  <character.skinbreaker>Skin Breaker</character.skinbreaker>
  <character.eyibug>Bloodworm</character.eyibug>
  <character.Eyi_hugger>Embracer</character.Eyi_hugger>
  <character.pgc>Sea of Miracles Heavy Guard</character.pgc>
  <character.adventists_heavy>Adventist Heavy Leader</character.adventists_heavy>
  <character.adventists>Adventist Armed Soldier</character.adventists>
  <character.Facility_security>Facility Security</character.Facility_security>
  <character.Facility_security_heavy>Facility Heavy Security</character.Facility_security_heavy>
  <character.Facility_security_outside>Facility Outer Security</character.Facility_security_outside>
  <charactername.tsm_outpost_combat_npc_mission>Sea of Miracles Soldier</charactername.tsm_outpost_combat_npc_mission>
  <charactername.tsm_adventists_prisoner>Captured Adventist Member</charactername.tsm_adventists_prisoner>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_time1>Decaying Material</entityname.tsm_mcrate_time1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_time1>A box of decaying material with only ten minutes of shelf life.</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_time1>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_water1>Boxed Leather</entityname.tsm_mcrate_water1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_water1>A full box of high-quality leather. If it gets wet, it will be damaged. Be careful, most people can’t afford to pay for this.</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_water1>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_shillok>Shirok's Treasure</entityname.tsm_mcrate_shillok>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_shillok>It's said that this pouch could contain anything. Why not break it down and see what you get?</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_shillok>
  <faction.tsm>The Sea of Miracles</faction.tsm>
  <faction.tsm.description>The Sea of Miracles Company has gradually evolved into a significant faction. With its wide-reaching influence and resources, the company’s role has expanded beyond mere commercial operations, extending into the political and military realms of the deep-sea world, forming a powerful faction with a profound impact on deep-sea exploration and regional security.</faction.tsm.description>
  <faction.tsm.shortdescription>Sea of Miracles is an outstanding multi-field enterprise. The company is renowned for its exceptional escort services, providing unparalleled safety guarantees, ensuring the safety of deep-sea explorers and merchant vessels.</faction.tsm.shortdescription>
  <randomnews35>A new submarine is clearing threats from the waters of Europa. The Coalition has responded positively and hopes more teams will join in to make the channels safer.</randomnews35>
  <randomnews36>Sea of Miracles has your back</randomnews36>
  <locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.abandoned>Sea of Miracles’s fortress city [previousname] has fallen.</locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.abandoned>
  <locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.none>Sea of Miracles’s fortress city [previousname] has relocated to a more suitable location.</locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.none>
  <locationchange.none.changeto.tsm_city>Sea of Miracles discovered the ecological zone [previousname] and established a fortress city there.</locationchange.none.changeto.tsm_city>
  <locationchange.abandoned.changeto.tsm_city>Sea of Miracles cleared the internal threats of [previousname] and established a city on this foundation.</locationchange.abandoned.changeto.tsm_city>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgeneric.nomoney.tsm>“If you're not capable and not planning to pay the deposit, don’t waste my precious nap time.”</eventtext.unlockpathgeneric.nomoney.tsm>
  <eventtext.unlockpath.refusebribe.tsm>Thought better of it</eventtext.unlockpath.refusebribe.tsm>
  <lockedpathtooltiptsmreputation>This passage has been sealed off by Sea of Miracles. If you want to continue, your reputation with ‖color:faction.tsm‖ Sea of Miracles must exceed [requiredreputation], and you must obtain the administrator's permission. You can view your current reputation in the info interface.\n\nCurrent Reputation: [currentreputation]</lockedpathtooltiptsmreputation>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc1>“You want to pass this checkpoint?”\nThe administrator looked up, his gaze sweeping through the fleet via the control panel's light screen, then skillfully operating the terminal,\n“Wait a moment, I need to verify your fleet’s records.”\nA few seconds later\n“Welcome, Captain. After review, your reputation is sufficient. Permission to travel to the Europan Ridge has been granted. The authorization has been synced to your terminal.”\nHe paused, a hint of seriousness flashing in his eyes\n“But, the Europan Ridge is far more perilous than previous routes. Deep-sea currents, unknown creatures, and wrecked ships may threaten your safety at any moment. Captain, please stay calm and cautious.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc2>“You want to dive into deeper waters?”\nThe administrator smiled faintly, lightly touching the terminal, “Hold on a moment, I need to pull up your records.”\nA few seconds later, the data on the screen made the administrator frown, “Sorry, according to the current records, you haven’t met the requirements to pass the blockade.”\n“But...” he paused, glancing from the terminal to you, with a slightly playful tone, “This is the Sea of Miracles, after all. In these waters, there are always exceptions. If you insist on heading deeper, we can make an exception—provided you pay a 2000mk deposit.”\nThe administrator leaned back in his chair, his gaze filled with a mix of anticipation and calculation, “Now, the decision is yours. What will you choose?”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1>2000MK, deal!</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.tsmc1>“Great! I like people with this kind of attitude. I’ll let the folks at the blockade know; you just go ahead.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.nomoney>“No money? Well, then I can’t help you. Your fleet’s records don’t look too promising. If you’re broke, consider earning some cash through bounties.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo2.tsmc1>“If you’re not capable and not planning to pay the deposit, don’t waste my precious rest time.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc1>“You want to head to the Aphotic Plateau?”\n“Please hold on a second,” the administrator’s fingers swiftly glided over the terminal.\nA moment later, the administrator smiled in satisfaction, “It seems you’ve been contributing a lot to the Ice Ridge. I’m pleased to announce—you now have access to the Aphotic Plateau.”\n“May you sail smoothly in those dark depths. Safe travels, Captain.”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc2>“You want to enter the Aphotic Plateau?”\nThe administrator squinted, lightly tapping the terminal, and chuckled softly after a moment, “Judging by the records, this doesn’t look too promising…”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1>“I understand, I understand, is 4500mk enough?”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.tsmc1>“Your records aren’t bad, but are you truly ready? This dangerous sea won’t accept just anyone.”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.nomoney>“Not enough money, huh? Well, we’ve recently posted some bounty missions, why not give them a shot?”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo2.tsmc1>“Whether you go or not, that’s not for us to decide, it’s up to you. After all, the Europa Ridge is a great place to live, isn’t it?”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc1>“Ah, it’s you! You’re the star fleet everyone’s been talking about, right? Your tales are all over Europa.”\n“Of course, of course, this means you’ve earned the right to traverse the Aphotic Plateau. You may now set sail for the Great Sea. Not many fleets have managed to make it there under the current circumstances.”\nThe administrator stood up and shook your hand, “I’ll notify the checkpoint ahead to allow your passage into the Abyss. May you proceed safely through those unfathomable waters.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc2>“My apologies,”\nThe administrator sighed, a hint of helplessness in his expression, “I know it hasn’t been easy for you to make it this far, you’ve overcome many obstacles. But we cannot risk letting an unqualified fleet venture into the Great Sea.”\nHe looked up, his tone softening slightly, “This is for your protection. I hope you understand, not everyone can handle the dangers lurking there.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1>“What if we pay a 9K deposit?”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.tsmc1>“According to our regulations, you can indeed pass,” he said slowly, his tone solemn.\n“But I must advise you to think carefully. The Great Sea is not a place to tread lightly.” He gazed at you, his voice low and full of meaning.\n“That sea holds endless unknowns and dangers, and not everyone returns from it. Please consider carefully.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.nomoney>“If you don’t have enough money, don’t push it. Besides, money isn’t everything—stay alive first, then talk.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo2.tsmc1>“As I said, there’s no need to go overboard. The Aphotic Plateau are great, livable, and Sea of Miracles's headquarters are there. Why not buy an apartment and retire?”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc1>The administrator saw you from afar and stood up, shaking your hand. “Look who it is! The famous star fleet! What can I do for you this time?”\nUpon hearing your request to travel to the Hydrothermal Wastes, the administrator’s expression stiffened slightly. He was silent for a moment, then spoke in a slow, deliberate tone: “The number of creatures in the next area is abnormally high, and the currents stirred by geothermal activity will make navigation even more dangerous.” He looked at you, as if gauging your resolve. “Are you truly prepared?”\nHe straightened up and saluted you. “Then, please be careful—do not be careless.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc2>“So you want to enter the Hydrothermal Wasteland? Many fleets have tried, and many have gone missing. This is the Sea of Miracles’s deposit system. If you’re determined to go, take a look.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1>“17000mk? No problem, I’ll transfer the money shortly.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.tsmc1>“Don’t rush. You can always reconsider. It’s rare to see someone who’s both earning money with their life and buying their way into danger. First time I’ve seen someone paying to die.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.nomoney>“Then don’t go. You need both money and life to enjoy it. As long as you’re alive, you’ll always have money.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo2.tsmc1>“Many could’ve stood where you are now, with the courage to press forward.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_1>Captain of Wolf Falcon Squad</npctitle.TSMnpc_1>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_2>Captain of Shadow-Stained Squad</npctitle.TSMnpc_2>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_4>Chief Instructor of Sea of Miracles</npctitle.TSMnpc_4>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_5>Acting Minister of Kyushu Operations Department</npctitle.TSMnpc_5>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_7>Bishop of the Adventist</npctitle.TSMnpc_7>
  <npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_npc>Sea of Miracles Sundown Operations Department</npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_npc>
  <npctitle.tsm_outpostmanager>Controller</npctitle.tsm_outpostmanager>
  <npctitle.tsm_wz_ff>Quartermaster</npctitle.tsm_wz_ff>
  <npctitle.tsm_caretakers>Route Manager</npctitle.tsm_caretakers>
  <npctitle.tsm_wz_ff_xbz>Beacon Station Manager</npctitle.tsm_wz_ff_xbz>
  <npctitle.tsm_bountyhunter>Sea of Miracles Bounty Task Distributor</npctitle.tsm_bountyhunter>
  <npctitle.tsm_gendarmerie>Sea of Miracles Military Police</npctitle.tsm_gendarmerie>
  <entityname.tsm_lighter>Old Lighter</entityname.tsm_lighter>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lighter>Want to smoke a cigarette?</entitydescription.tsm_lighter>
  <entityname.tsm_marlboro_cigar>Marlboro Cigarette</entityname.tsm_marlboro_cigar>
  <entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_cigar>Man always remember love because of romantic only\nSlowly reduces mental stress, psychosis, and delirium poisoning</entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_cigar>
  <entityname.tsm_marlboro_box>Pack of Marlboro</entityname.tsm_marlboro_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_box>Smoking Marlboro gives you more masculinity\nContains 8 Marlboro cigarettes</entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_box>
  <entityname.tsm_Chinese_cigar>Huazi Cigarette</entityname.tsm_Chinese_cigar>
  <entitydescription.tsm_Chinese_cigar>Every puff of Huazi shows noble quality\nQuickly relieves mental stress and psychosis, and provides resistance to mental stress</entitydescription.tsm_Chinese_cigar>
  <entityname.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>Pack of Huazi</entityname.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>Distinct character, elegant style, beauty of Huazi\nContains 6 Huazi cigarettes</entitydescription.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>
  <entityname.tsm_universe_cigar>Cosmos Cigarette</entityname.tsm_universe_cigar>
  <entitydescription.tsm_universe_cigar>The top choice for superhumans on Europa\nQuickly relieves mental stress and delirium poisoning</entitydescription.tsm_universe_cigar>
  <entityname.tsm_universe_box>Pack of Cosmos</entityname.tsm_universe_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_universe_box>Smoke Cosmos, become a Europa person\nContains 6 Cosmos cigarettes</entitydescription.tsm_universe_box>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_relics>Plague Organism</entityname.tsm_eyi_relics>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_relics>A product not belonging to this world, might need an abnormal affairs containment box</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_relics>
  <entityname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>Plague Type III Suppressant</entityname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>
  <entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>Used to suppress the growth of flesh embryos and prevent them from entering the next stage, but it cannot fully cure</entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>
  <entityname.tsm_virusstage_clear>Plague Potent Eliminator</entityname.tsm_virusstage_clear>
  <entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_clear>Directly removes flesh embryos from the body, but causes physical harm.</entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_clear>
  <entityname.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>Potent Plague Eliminator</entityname.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>
  <entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>Used for potent elimination of the plague (Flesh Embryo Stage 2), at the cost of significant bodily harm.</entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>Plague Norm</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>Stable state: Dormant inside your body, will accelerate transformation if injected with living plague\nA norm developed by Sea of Miracles to enhance the human body, with different effects at various stages</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>Plague Stability Enhancer</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>An enhancer from an unknown origin, its purpose to increase or decrease plague norm stability is unclear</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>Plague Stability Enhancer</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>An enhancer from an unknown origin, its purpose to increase or decrease plague norm stability is unclear</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer I</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 1‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer II</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 2‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer III</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 3‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer IV</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 4‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>Plague Weakening Enhancer I</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 1‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>Plague Weakening Enhancer II</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 2‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>Plague Weakening Enhancer III</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 3‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>Plague Weakening Enhancer IV</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 4‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>
  <entityname.tsm_walkman>This Night, No Dreams of Parting</entityname.tsm_walkman>
  <entitydescription.tsm_walkman>A portable player, can play audio tapes obtained from bosses or purchased from the station.</entitydescription.tsm_walkman>
  <entityname.tsm_suger>Sugar's Transmogrifier</entityname.tsm_suger>
  <entitydescription.tsm_suger>Sugar's transmogrifier, can transform into Sugar's appearance</entitydescription.tsm_suger>
  <entityname.suger_combat_uniform>Sugar's Combat Suit</entityname.suger_combat_uniform>
  <entitydescription.suger_combat_uniform>Uses a durable bulletproof synthetic fiber to protect vulnerable areas, but heavily tailored for flexibility. Strangely, the outfit includes an old captain's jacket that looks oversized and worn, which, according to Sugar, symbolizes "responsibility and duty."</entitydescription.suger_combat_uniform>
  <entityname.suger_clothes>Sugar's Hoodie</entityname.suger_clothes>
  <entitydescription.suger_clothes>A hoodie that Sugar often wears while resting, light and comfortable</entitydescription.suger_clothes>
  <entityname.tsm_grey_pupils>‖color:221,106,29,255‖Gray Eyes‖color:end‖</entityname.tsm_grey_pupils>
  <entitydescription.tsm_grey_pupils>‖color:221,106,29,255‖Lerentine's sidearm, uses hand cannon rounds\nIt is said to be her squad leader's gun from when she was part of the Advanced Operations Department. During an ambush, the leader was shot and killed while saving her. She then took the gun, donned the leader's helmet, and gave the orders.\nShe became known as the "Child of Doom," Sea of Miracles's child, and your last savior when death looms over you.‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_grey_pupils>
  <entityname.tsm_common_uniform>Standard Uniform·Shirt</entityname.tsm_common_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_common_uniform>Standard issue uniform from Kyushu Operations Department, but the female version</entitydescription.tsm_common_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_lerentine>Lerentine's Transmogrifier</entityname.tsm_lerentine>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lerentine>Lerentine's transmogrifier, can transform into Lerentine's appearance</entitydescription.tsm_lerentine>
  <entityname.tsm_hat_officer>Officer's Cap</entityname.tsm_hat_officer>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hat_officer />
  <entityname.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>‖color:150,0,0,255‖PX-18‖color:end‖</entityname.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>Uses a‖color:150,0,0,255‖9mm‖color:end‖pistol magazine</entitydescription.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>
  <entityname.hxl_knife>‖color:150,0,0,255‖Illusion‖color:end‖</entityname.hxl_knife>
  <entitydescription.hxl_knife>‖color:150,0,0,255‖A False Reality‖color:end‖</entitydescription.hxl_knife>
  <entityname.tsm_hxl_unform>Clothes of Phantom Lang</entityname.tsm_hxl_unform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hxl_unform>Lang\nEntity under the Phantom</entitydescription.tsm_hxl_unform>
  <entityname.tsm_9_mag>Pistol Magazine (9mm)</entityname.tsm_9_mag>
  <entitydescription.tsm_9_mag>Holds 18 rounds of 9mm ammunition</entitydescription.tsm_9_mag>
  <entityname.tsm_identifier>T.S.M Allied Identification Code</entityname.tsm_identifier>
  <entitydescription.tsm_identifier>A common identification code within the Sea of Miracles, which you can request various services from the Sea of Miracles logistics department</entitydescription.tsm_identifier>
  <entityname.tsm_pgcflare>Guardian Landing Pod Indicator</entityname.tsm_pgcflare>
  <entitydescription.tsm_pgcflare>'Remember the feeling of asking for help, call Sea of Miracles'\n\nUsage: Throw it out and wait patiently. (Exists only in one round)</entitydescription.tsm_pgcflare>
  <entityname.tsm_wz_cl_flare>Mineral Supply Drop Indicator</entityname.tsm_wz_cl_flare>
  <entitydescription.tsm_wz_cl_flare>After being thrown, the Sea of Miracles will receive a signal and drop a supply pod based on the coordinates</entitydescription.tsm_wz_cl_flare>
  <entityname.tsm_wz_yl_flare>Medical Supply Drop Indicator</entityname.tsm_wz_yl_flare>
  <entitydescription.tsm_wz_yl_flare>After being thrown, the Sea of Miracles will receive a signal and drop a medical supply pod based on the coordinates</entitydescription.tsm_wz_yl_flare>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>T.S.M Mineral Supply Box</entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>A common supply box in the Sea of Miracles, which randomly yields various common minerals when dismantled\nThese have just been packed and sent from the mines; if you think it's little, I think it's little too</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>T.S.M Mineral Supply Box</entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>A common supply box in the Sea of Miracles, which randomly yields various common minerals when dismantled\nThese have just been packed and sent from the mines; if you think it's little, I think it's little too</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>T.S.M Medical Supply Box</entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>A common medical supply box in the Sea of Miracles, which randomly yields various medical supplies when dismantled\nUrgent! Urgent! The brothers on the front line are still waiting for rescue!</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>
  <entityname.tsm_suit_O5>Suit</entityname.tsm_suit_O5>
  <entitydescription.tsm_suit_O5>Your second layer of skin, enveloping power and confidence</entitydescription.tsm_suit_O5>
  <entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>T.S.M Gendarmerie Uniform</entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>
  <entitydescription.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>The gendarmerie uniform of the Sea of Miracles, mainly maintains troop discipline and ensures the execution of orders</entitydescription.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>
  <entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_hat>T.S.M Gendarmerie Hat</entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_hat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_gendarmerie_hat />
  <entityname.tsm_advancedcombatsuit>Damaged Military Advanced Protective Suit</entityname.tsm_advancedcombatsuit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advancedcombatsuit>Most of the external armor has been damaged, can only withstand water pressure of 5000 meters.</entitydescription.tsm_advancedcombatsuit>
  <entityname.tsm_orangeconstant>Damaged Orange Wuchang Protective Suit</entityname.tsm_orangeconstant>
  <entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant>This protective suit was damaged in combat, many functions are disabled, and the pressure resistance is only 5000 meters</entitydescription.tsm_orangeconstant>
  <entityname.tsm_rz_2a>Combat Outfit Type 2A</entityname.tsm_rz_2a>
  <entitydescription.tsm_rz_2a>Unlike Type 2B, it does not come with a weapon, merely used as a full-body exoskeleton</entitydescription.tsm_rz_2a>
  <entityname.lm_rapidreaction_helmet>Coalition Rapid Reaction Force Helmet</entityname.lm_rapidreaction_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_helmet />
  <entityname.lm_rapidreaction_vest>Coalition Rapid Reaction Force Bulletproof Vest</entityname.lm_rapidreaction_vest>
  <entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_vest />
  <entityname.lm_rapidreaction_uniform>Coalition Rapid Reaction Force Combat Suit</entityname.lm_rapidreaction_uniform>
  <entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_uniform />
  <entityname.tsm_old_uniform>Old-fashioned Combat Suit</entityname.tsm_old_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_old_uniform />
  <entityname.adventists_uniform>Leader's Robe of the Descending Faction</entityname.adventists_uniform>
  <entitydescription.adventists_uniform />
  <entityname.adventists_Wind_proof>Descending Faction Windbreaker Safety Jacket</entityname.adventists_Wind_proof>
  <entitydescription.adventists_Wind_proof />
  <entityname.tsm_rz_pirent_m>Combat Outfit Thief Type</entityname.tsm_rz_pirent_m>
  <entitydescription.tsm_rz_pirent_m>Thieves, after attacking the Sea of Miracles cargo ship, acquired Combat Outfit Type 2A and modified it according to their own ideas</entitydescription.tsm_rz_pirent_m>
  <entityname.tsm_fog>Fog</entityname.tsm_fog>
  <entityname.tsm_slogan>Slogan of the T.S.M</entityname.tsm_slogan>
  <entityname.tsm_mech>T.S.M Mecha Decoration</entityname.tsm_mech>
  <entityname.tsm_bossitem>T.S.M Boss Drop Decoration</entityname.tsm_bossitem>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental>Evil Plague Flesh Decoration</entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental>
  <entityname.tsm_hf>Propaganda Banner</entityname.tsm_hf>
  <talentname.tsm_ei_talent_test>Experimental Evil Plague Normal State</talentname.tsm_ei_talent_test>
  <talentname.tsm_ei_talent_stabilise>Stable Evil Plague Normal State</talentname.tsm_ei_talent_stabilise>
  <talentname.tsm_ei>Masterpiece</talentname.tsm_ei>
  <talentname.tsm_all_ru>Pure Evil Plague State</talentname.tsm_all_ru>
  <talentname.tsm_warlord>Violent Warlord</talentname.tsm_warlord>
  <talentname.tsm_specops>Special Forces</talentname.tsm_specops>
  <talentname.tsm_beatcop>Inspection Police</talentname.tsm_beatcop>
  <talentname.tsm_bleeding_outpost_sundown>Coagulant</talentname.tsm_bleeding_outpost_sundown>
  <talentname.suger_tail_handle>Sugar-tail Transmogrifier</talentname.suger_tail_handle>
  <talentdescription.suger_tail_handle>When you wear the device, you will grow cat ears and a cat tail.</talentdescription.suger_tail_handle>
  <talentname.tsm_ai_outpost>Stable Evil Plague Normal State of the Sea of Miracles</talentname.tsm_ai_outpost>
  <talentdescription.tsm_ai_outpost>Alter part of the DNA sequence to make the body reject foreign parasites.</talentdescription.tsm_ai_outpost>
  <talentname.tsm_eyi_instability>Unstable Evil Plague Anomaly State</talentname.tsm_eyi_instability>
  <talentdescription.tsm_eyi_instability />
  <afflictionname.tsm_ondeath>Dead Sea</afflictionname.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_ondeath>What are you seeking?</afflictiondescription.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_ondeath>What are you seeking?</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_ondeath>What are you seeking?</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictionname.tsm_eyi_attack>Combat Evil Plague Normal State</afflictionname.tsm_eyi_attack>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_attack>The Evil Plague within you is in a stable state, continuously providing bonuses in combat.</afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_attack>
  <afflictionname.tsm_stress_resistance>Strong Will</afflictionname.tsm_stress_resistance>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_stress_resistance>Your will is very firm at this moment, able to withstand the torment of other things on your mind.</afflictiondescription.tsm_stress_resistance>
  <afflictionname.tsm_stress>Mental Stress</afflictionname.tsm_stress>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_stress>You are currently feeling very tense and in pain.</afflictiondescription.tsm_stress>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_stress>Committed suicide.</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_stress>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_stress>You committed suicide.</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_stress>
  <afflictionname.tsm_eyi_provocative>Flesh Information Pheromone</afflictionname.tsm_eyi_provocative>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_provocative>You have been bitten by a rotting corpse; now the tearing wounds and bites you receive will increase, and enemies will be more likely to target you.</afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_provocative>
  <afflictionname.tsm_virusstage>Flesh Embryo</afflictionname.tsm_virusstage>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage>The Evil Plague virus is using your body as a breeding ground, forcibly altering the host's genes to match the Skin Breaker.</afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage>
  <afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_deep>Evil Plague</afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage_deep>The host's genes have been altered; this situation is basically irreversible, and the body is undergoing changes.</afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_virusstage_deep>I swim upstream, you are like in the center of the water.</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_virusstage_deep>I swim upstream, you are like in the center of the water.</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_bite>Insect Bite</afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_bite>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_bite>You have been bitten by an Evil Plague bloodworm.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_bite>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_monster_50>Broken Bones</afflictionname.tsmmission_monster_50>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_monster_50>You feel as if your bones have broken/n At this moment, the tearing and biting damage you suffer will increase.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_monster_50>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>T.S.M Sundown Stable Evil Plague State</afflictionname.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>Alters part of the DNA sequence to make the body reject foreign parasites.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>
  <afflictionname.tsm_eyi_stable_state>Stable Evil Plague Normal State</afflictionname.tsm_eyi_stable_state>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_0_1>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure, require no oxygen, increase maximum health by 30%, and will no longer become addicted to drugs. Burns will recover quickly, and you will rapidly heal from Flesh Embryos and Husk Infection.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_0_1>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_1_4>At this stage, you will not need oxygen and will gain 30% swimming speed.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_1_4>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_4_8>At this stage, you will gain immunity to all toxins.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_4_8>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_8_16>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure of 6213 meters and slowly heal from hypoxia.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_8_16>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_16_22>At this stage, you will quickly heal from bleeding and blood loss.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_16_22>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_22_28>At this stage, you will gain 30% physical damage resistance.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_22_28>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_28_33>At this stage, you will gain a 10% attack speed increase for ranged weapons and reduce spread by 20%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_28_33>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_33_37>At this stage, you will gain 50% resistance to stuns and burns.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_33_37>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_37_39>At this stage, you will slowly heal physical damage and burns.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_37_39>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_39_42>At this stage, you will gain 50% resistance to Opioid poisoning, Withdrawal, Addiction, Alcohol poisoning, Psychosis, Husk Infection, as well as Acid Burns which will heal slowly.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_39_42>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_42_44>At this stage, you will gain 25% attack power, 50% melee strike force, and 10% turret attack speed.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_42_44>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_44_48>At this stage, you will have 55% bleeding resistance.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_44_48>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_48_55>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure of 5112 meters.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_48_55>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_55_59>At this stage, all your skill levels will increase by 18, and repair speed will increase by 44%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_55_59>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_59_63>At this stage, you will gain 30% melee attack speed, 20% movement speed, and 40% stun resistance.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_59_63>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_63_65>At this stage, you will gain 30% damage resistance and 30% maximum health.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_63_65>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_65_69>At this stage, you will gain the ability to slowly heal from all toxins.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_65_69>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_69_72>At this stage, you can recover from stun faster, increase attack power by 30% and ranged attack speed by 5%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_69_72>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_72_76>At this stage, you will never die.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_72_76>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_76_83>At this stage, your item crafting speed will increase by 150%, and crafting level will increase by 2.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_76_83>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_83_85>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure of 6177 meters and will not need oxygen.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_83_85>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_85_90>At this stage, you will gain 25% resistance to physical damage and burns, and gain 25% attack power.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_85_90>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_90_95>At this stage, all healing effects on you will increase by 100%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_90_95>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_95_100>At this stage, part of your body’s DNA sequence will change, beginning to reject foreign parasites.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_95_100>
  <locationdescription.tsm_city>The largest city under the Sea of Miracles, bustling with people, with comprehensive facilities and services.</locationdescription.tsm_city>
  <locationname.tsm_city>Sea of Miracles Fortress City</locationname.tsm_city>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_city>[name] Station</locationnameformat.tsm_city>
  <locationname.tsm_mine>Sea of Miracles Mining Station</locationname.tsm_mine>
  <locationdescription.tsm_mine>A mineral mining site under the Sea of Miracles, where you can go deep into the mines to mine.</locationdescription.tsm_mine>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_mine>[name] Station</locationnameformat.tsm_mine>
  <locationname.tsm_military>Sea of Miracles Armed Division</locationname.tsm_military>
  <locationdescription.tsm_military>A military stronghold under the Sea of Miracles.</locationdescription.tsm_military>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_military>[name] Station</locationnameformat.tsm_military>
  <locationname.tsm_city.0>Xige</locationname.tsm_city.0>
  <locationname.tsm_city.1>Three Gods Hill</locationname.tsm_city.1>
  <locationname.tsm_city.2>Huai Shuo</locationname.tsm_city.2>
  <locationname.tsm_city.3>Yongan</locationname.tsm_city.3>
  <locationname.tsm_city.4>Chang'an</locationname.tsm_city.4>
  <locationname.tsm_city.5>Fu Ming</locationname.tsm_city.5>
  <locationname.tsm_city.6>Huo Lu</locationname.tsm_city.6>
  <loadingscreentip>Go try the Touhou Deep Sea Operation Team!</loadingscreentip>
  <entityname.tsm_touhou>Linked Content - Touhou Deep Sea Operation Team</entityname.tsm_touhou>
  <!-- OutpostEvents.xml -->
  <tsm.tl1>Hello, I am the quartermaster of the Sea of Miracles. How may I assist you?</tsm.tl1>
  <tsm.tl2>Exchange items with friendly identification codes.</tsm.tl2>
  <tsm.tl3>Due to the current chaotic situation with the factions, the outlook is not good. For now, we can only offer these exchanges.</tsm.tl3>
  <tsm.tl4>Exchange for mineral supplies.</tsm.tl4>
  <tsm.tl5>Please take your items.</tsm.tl5>
  <tsm.tl6>You don't have any friendly identification codes. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl6>
  <tsm.tl7>Exchange for medical supplies.</tsm.tl7>
  <tsm.tl8>Please take your items.</tsm.tl8>
  <tsm.tl9>You don't have any friendly identification codes. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl9>
  <tsm.tl10>Exchange for escort services.</tsm.tl10>
  <tsm.tl11>Please take your items.</tsm.tl11>
  <tsm.tl12>You don't have any friendly identification codes. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl12>
  <tsm.tl13>I'll come back later.</tsm.tl13>
  <tsm.tl14>I'll be waiting for your visit anytime.</tsm.tl14>
  <tsm.tl15>Exchange items with Sea of Miracles reputation points.</tsm.tl15>
  <tsm.tl16>You need to have over 25 reputation points to exchange for supplies.</tsm.tl16>
  <tsm.tl17>Exchange for mineral supplies.</tsm.tl17>
  <tsm.tl18>Please take your items.</tsm.tl18>
  <tsm.tl19>You don't have enough reputation points. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl19>
  <tsm.tl20>Exchange for medical supplies.</tsm.tl20>
  <tsm.tl21>Please take your items.</tsm.tl21>
  <tsm.tl22>You don't have enough reputation points. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl22>
  <tsm.tl23>Exchange for escort services.</tsm.tl23>
  <tsm.tl24>Please take your items.</tsm.tl24>
  <tsm.tl25>You don't have enough reputation points. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl25>
  <tsm.tl26>I'll come back later.</tsm.tl26>
  <tsm.tl27>I'll be waiting for your visit anytime.</tsm.tl27>
  <tsm.tl28>I'll come back later.</tsm.tl28>
  <tsm.tl29>I'll be waiting for your visit anytime.</tsm.tl29>
  <tsm.tl30>Welcome to the Sea of Miracles Supply Beacon Station. How may I assist you?</tsm.tl30>
  <tsm.tl31>Exchange items with friendly identification codes.</tsm.tl31>
  <tsm.tl32>Due to the current chaotic situation with the factions, the outlook is not good. For now, we can only offer these exchanges.</tsm.tl32>
  <tsm.tl33>Exchange for mineral supplies.</tsm.tl33>
  <tsm.tl34>Please take your items.</tsm.tl34>
  <tsm.tl35>You don't have any friendly identification codes. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl35>
  <tsm.tl36>Exchange for medical supplies.</tsm.tl36>
  <tsm.tl37>Please take your items.</tsm.tl37>
  <tsm.tl38>You don't have any friendly identification codes. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl38>
  <tsm.tl39>Exchange for escort services.</tsm.tl39>
  <tsm.tl40>Please take your items.</tsm.tl40>
  <tsm.tl41>You don't have any friendly identification codes. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl41>
  <tsm.tl42>I'll come back later.</tsm.tl42>
  <tsm.tl43>I'll be waiting for your visit anytime.</tsm.tl43>
  <tsm.tl44>Exchange items with the Sea of Miracles reputation points.</tsm.tl44>
  <tsm.tl45>You need to have over 25 reputation points to exchange for supplies.</tsm.tl45>
  <tsm.tl46>Exchange for mineral supplies.</tsm.tl46>
  <tsm.tl47>Please take your items.</tsm.tl47>
  <tsm.tl48>You don't have enough reputation points. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl48>
  <tsm.tl49>Exchange for medical supplies.</tsm.tl49>
  <tsm.tl50>Please take your items.</tsm.tl50>
  <tsm.tl51>You don't have enough reputation points. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl51>
  <tsm.tl52>Exchange for escort services.</tsm.tl52>
  <tsm.tl53>Please take your items.</tsm.tl53>
  <tsm.tl54>You don't have enough reputation points. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.tl54>
  <tsm.tl55>I'll come back later.</tsm.tl55>
  <tsm.tl56>I'll be waiting for your visit anytime.</tsm.tl56>
  <tsm.tl57>I'll come back later.</tsm.tl57>
  <tsm.tl58>I'll be waiting for your visit anytime.</tsm.tl58>
  <tsm.tl59>Hello, I am Phantom Lang, the head of the Sea of Miracles Armory. I'm here to issue bounties from the Sea of Miracles to passing captains.</tsm.tl59>
  <tsm.tl60>You are... Phantom Lang?</tsm.tl60>
  <tsm.tl61>Ah, yes, that's my nickname. You can call me that too.</tsm.tl61>
  <tsm.tl62>No, I mean: I’ve met someone called "Phantom Lang" before...</tsm.tl62>
  <tsm.tl63>Oh, I know what you mean. Those were my people. They were issuing commands on my behalf, but many of them are now missing...gone without a trace. If you see them, please let me know.</tsm.tl63>
  <tsm.tl64>Oh, I see. Alright, alright. So, what tasks do you have now?</tsm.tl64>
  <tsm.tl65>Hmm... I've already sent the tasks to your panel. Please proceed with caution.\nAnd... try to stay alive.</tsm.tl65>
  <tsm.tl66>This route is now under a blockade by The Sea of Miracles. Turn back immediately, or we will resort to forceful expulsion!</tsm.tl66>
  <tsm.tl67>This is your final warning! Turn back now!</tsm.tl67>
  <tsm.tl68>You see a man acting suspiciously, so you approach him to see what he's up to.</tsm.tl68>
  <tsm.tl69>"What are you doing?" you say while putting a hand on his shoulder.</tsm.tl69>
  <tsm.tl70>The man is clearly startled. After glancing at the device in his hand, he stares at you blankly. As soon as you realize what he's holding, he takes off running.</tsm.tl70>
  <tsm.tl71>"Don't run!" Just as you start to chase after him, alarms begin blaring throughout the station.</tsm.tl71>
  <tsm.tl72>T.S.M: \nUnknown hostile forces have been detected, T-71 defense protocol has been activated.\nThe entire station is now under lockdown. All civilians are urged to remain calm and proceed to the nearest safety shelter. The Sundown Operations Department will begin clearing out the intruders. Please refrain from taking any unauthorized actions and wait for the situation to stabilize.</tsm.tl72>
  <!-- OutpostEvents_tsm.xml -->
  <tsm.tl_p_1>Hello, I am Phantom Lang, the head of the Armed Forces of the Sea of Miracles. I am still searching for my missing team members.</tsm.tl_p_1>
  <tsm.tl_p_2>Sorry to bother you.</tsm.tl_p_2>
  <tsm.tl_p_3>I'm handling business, don't disturb me.</tsm.tl_p_3>
  <tsm.tl_p_4>Exchange items</tsm.tl_p_4>
  <tsm.tl_p_5>Fair prices, honest trade.</tsm.tl_p_5>
  <tsm.tl_p_6>400 MK to exchange for Sugar's Transmogrifier</tsm.tl_p_6>
  <tsm.tl_p_7>Hey, these are rare treasures, though they’re all knock-offs... replicas. But I'm raising MK to repair my drone Nancy, otherwise, I wouldn't be willing to sell them to you.</tsm.tl_p_7>
  <tsm.tl_p_8>300 MK to exchange for Sugar's Combat Suit</tsm.tl_p_8>
  <tsm.tl_p_9>250 MK to exchange for Sugar's Hoodie</tsm.tl_p_9>
  <tsm.tl_p_10>450 MK to exchange for Sugar's's Battle Axe</tsm.tl_p_10>
  <tsm.tl_p_11>150 MK to exchange for Navy Officer's Large Hat</tsm.tl_p_11>
  <tsm.tl_p_12>2300 MK to exchange for Icarus Hand Cannon</tsm.tl_p_12>
  <tsm.tl_p_13>800 MK to exchange for 6 Hand Cannon Bullets</tsm.tl_p_13>
  <tsm.tl_p_14>Six bullets, enough to take down twelve people.</tsm.tl_p_14>
  <tsm.tl_p_15>1000 MK to exchange for Medical Supplies</tsm.tl_p_15>
  <tsm.tl_p_16>Special supplies from the Sea of Miracles.</tsm.tl_p_16>
  <tsm.tl_p_17>Not much left, see what you need.</tsm.tl_p_17>
  <tsm.tl_p_18>400 MK to exchange for Lerentine Transmogrifier</tsm.tl_p_18>
  <tsm.tl_p_19>Don’t use it for bad things!</tsm.tl_p_19>
  <tsm.tl_p_20>300 MK to exchange for Women's Uniform</tsm.tl_p_20>
  <tsm.tl_p_21>This is a women's uniform from Kyushu.</tsm.tl_p_21>
  <tsm.tl_p_22>2600 MK to exchange for Grey Eye</tsm.tl_p_22>
  <tsm.tl_p_23>This gun has been with me for a long time. If you're worthy, take it.</tsm.tl_p_23>
  <tsm.tl_p_24>200 MK to exchange for Officer's Hat</tsm.tl_p_24>
  <tsm.tl_p_25>A symbol of power.</tsm.tl_p_25>
  <tsm.tl_p_26>350 MK to exchange for Suit</tsm.tl_p_26>
  <tsm.tl_p_27>Looks nice.</tsm.tl_p_27>
  <tsm.tl_p_28>Think carefully before pulling the trigger.</tsm.tl_p_28>
  <tsm.tl_p_29>800 MK to exchange for Supplies</tsm.tl_p_29>

  <afflictionname.tsmmission_ai_stun>Stun Recovery</afflictionname.tsmmission_ai_stun>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_rev>Recovery</afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_rev>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_defend>Damage Resistance</afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_defend>
  <afflictionname.tsm_eyi_instability>Unstable Plague Abnormal State</afflictionname.tsm_eyi_instability>
  <entityname.tsm_blastshield_small>Round Shield</entityname.tsm_blastshield_small>
  <entityname.tsm_blastshield_big>Square Shield</entityname.tsm_blastshield_big>
  <entityname.tsmmission_handgun_b>Legacy</entityname.tsmmission_handgun_b>
  <entityname.tsmmission_handgun_o>Legacy</entityname.tsmmission_handgun_o>
  <entityname.tsmmission_assaultrifle_m>Assault Rifle</entityname.tsmmission_assaultrifle_m>
  <entityname.tsmmission_hmg_m>Heavy Machine Gun</entityname.tsmmission_hmg_m>
  <entityname.tsmmission_stunbaton_m>Special Electric Baton</entityname.tsmmission_stunbaton_m>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_pqc_m>Wall Breaching Hammer</entityname.tsmmissions_pqc_m>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_pmf_m>Door Breaching Axe</entityname.tsmmissions_pmf_m>
  <entityname.tsm_facility_med_uniform>Facility Doctor Uniform</entityname.tsm_facility_med_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_facility_security_uniform_b>Facility Security Uniform</entityname.tsm_facility_security_uniform_b>
  <entityname.tsm_facility_security_uniform_w>Facility Security Uniform</entityname.tsm_facility_security_uniform_w>
  <entityname.tsm_facility_security_vest>Facility Security Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_facility_security_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_facility_security_vest_heavy>Facility Security Heavy Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_facility_security_vest_heavy>
  <entityname.tsm_facility_security_helmet_w>Facility Security Helmet</entityname.tsm_facility_security_helmet_w>
  <entityname.tsm_facility_security_helmet_y>Facility Security Helmet</entityname.tsm_facility_security_helmet_y>
  <entityname.tsm_peripheral_security_uniform>Facility Perimeter Security Uniform</entityname.tsm_peripheral_security_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_peripheral_security_vest>Facility Perimeter Security Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_peripheral_security_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_peripheral_security_helmet>Facility Perimeter Security Helmet</entityname.tsm_peripheral_security_helmet>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_snow>Snowing</entityname.tsmmissions_snow>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_rain>Raining</entityname.tsmmissions_rain>

  <entityname.tsm_land_rs>Riot Squad Drop Pod</entityname.tsm_land_rs>
  <entityname.tsm_land_mtf>Vanguard Unit Drop Pod</entityname.tsm_land_mtf>
  <entityname.tsm_land_corrode>Corrosion Drop Pod</entityname.tsm_land_corrode>
  <entityname.tsm_land_wz_cl>Supply Drop Pod</entityname.tsm_land_wz_cl>
  <entityname.tsm_land_wz_yl>Medical Drop Pod</entityname.tsm_land_wz_yl>
  <entityname.tsm_danger_box>Sea of Miracles Anomaly Containment Box</entityname.tsm_danger_box>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_trap>Rotting Body Clamp</entityname.tsm_eyi_trap>
  <entityname.tsm_needletube_empty>Empty Syringe</entityname.tsm_needletube_empty>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_embryo>Flesh Embryo</entityname.tsm_eyi_embryo>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_glandular>Genetic Material</entityname.tsm_eyi_glandular>
  <entityname.tsm_touhou_4>Hakurei Reimu</entityname.tsm_touhou_4>
  <entityname.tsm_touhou_1>Touhou Flower Ornament</entityname.tsm_touhou_1>
  <entityname.tsm_touhou_2>Touhou Flower Ornament</entityname.tsm_touhou_2>
  <entityname.tsm_touhou_3>Touhou Flower Ornament</entityname.tsm_touhou_3>
  <entityname.tsm_black_stain>Black Stain 1</entityname.tsm_black_stain>
  <entityname.tsm_black_stain_1>Black Stain 2</entityname.tsm_black_stain_1>
  <entityname.tsm_blood_big>Large Bloodstain</entityname.tsm_blood_big>
  <entityname.tsm_stain_1>Stain 1</entityname.tsm_stain_1>
  <entityname.tsm_stain_2>Stain 2</entityname.tsm_stain_2>
  <entityname.tsm_blood_stain>Bloodstain</entityname.tsm_blood_stain>
  <entityname.tsm_stain_sand>Sand Stain</entityname.tsm_stain_sand>
  <entityname.tsm_blood_1>Blood Splatter 1</entityname.tsm_blood_1>
  <entityname.tsm_blood_2>Blood Splatter 2</entityname.tsm_blood_2>
  <entityname.tsm_blood_3>Blood Splatter 3</entityname.tsm_blood_3>
  <entityname.tsm_blood_4>Blood Splatter 4</entityname.tsm_blood_4>
  <entityname.tsm_paint_1>Paint Splatter 1</entityname.tsm_paint_1>
  <entityname.tsm_paint_2>Paint Splatter 2</entityname.tsm_paint_2>
  <entityname.tsm_paint_3>Paint Splatter 3</entityname.tsm_paint_3>
  <entityname.tsm_paint_4>Paint Splatter 4</entityname.tsm_paint_4>
  <entityname.tsm_rz1>Military Exosuit</entityname.tsm_rz1>
  <entityname.tsm_rz2>Military Exosuit</entityname.tsm_rz2>
  <entityname.tsm_rz3>Military Exosuit</entityname.tsm_rz3>
  <entityname.tsm_mvdxe>Witch's Jaw</entityname.tsm_mvdxe>
  <entityname.tsm_lldyj>Thunder Dragon's Eye</entityname.tsm_lldyj>
  <entityname.tsm_hyddx>Plague Venom Gland</entityname.tsm_hyddx>
  <entityname.tsm_ddbm>Wailing Earth</entityname.tsm_ddbm>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental1>Flesh Decoration</entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental2>Flesh Decoration</entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental3>Flesh Decoration</entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental3>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental4>Flesh Decoration</entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental4>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental5>Flesh Decoration</entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental5>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_7229>Number</entityname.tsm_eyi_7229>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_deadbody1>Corpse</entityname.tsm_eyi_deadbody1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_deadbody2>Corpse</entityname.tsm_eyi_deadbody2>
  <entityname.tsm_hf_1>Banner</entityname.tsm_hf_1>
  <entityname.tsm_hf_2>Banner</entityname.tsm_hf_2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_statues_1>Plague Statue</entityname.tsm_eyi_statues_1>
  <entityname.tsm_egg>Egg</entityname.tsm_egg>
  <entityname.tsm_mission_egg>Beacon Base</entityname.tsm_mission_egg>
  <entityname.tsm_mission_husk_box>Living Husk Box</entityname.tsm_mission_husk_box>
  
  <entityname.tsm_ai_eyi_outpost_sundown>Sea of Miracles Station Security Plague Injector</entityname.tsm_ai_eyi_outpost_sundown>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_instability>Unstable Plague Abnormal Injector</entityname.tsm_eyi_instability>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc>Event Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm1>tsm1 Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm1>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm2>tsm2 Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm2>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm3>tsm3 Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm3>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm4>tsm4 Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm4>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm5>tsm5 Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm5>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm6>tsm6 Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_tsm6>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_quartermaster>Quartermaster Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_npc_quartermaster>
  <entityname.tsm_event_spawn_outpost_invasions_coalition>Station Invasion Generator</entityname.tsm_event_spawn_outpost_invasions_coalition>
  <entityname.tsm_event_xbz_bg>Beacon Supply Generator</entityname.tsm_event_xbz_bg>
  <entityname.tsm_event_outpost_enhance>Station Security Enhancement Generator</entityname.tsm_event_outpost_enhance>
  <entityname.tsm_headset_hxl>Lang Transmogrifier Device</entityname.tsm_headset_hxl>
  <entityname.tsm_hxl>Lang Transmogrifier Device</entityname.tsm_hxl>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hxl>Lang’s Headphones, Can Morph Into Lang</entitydescription.tsm_hxl>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_hx870>Disillusion 870</entityname.tsmmissions_hx870>
  <entityname.tsm_hxl_unform_ai>Lang Uniform</entityname.tsm_hxl_unform_ai>
  <entityname.tsm_headset_lerentine>Lerentine Transmogrifier Device</entityname.tsm_headset_lerentine>
  <entityname.tsm_lerentine_uniform>Lerentine Uniform</entityname.tsm_lerentine_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lerentine_uniform></entitydescription.tsm_lerentine_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_headset_suger>Sugar Transmogrifier Device</entityname.tsm_headset_suger>
  <entityname.tsm_suger_uniform>Sugar Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_suger_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_suger_uniform></entitydescription.tsm_suger_uniform>
  <entityname.猜疑链>Chain of Suspicion</entityname.猜疑链>
  <entityname.降神典仪>Descent Ritual</entityname.降神典仪>
  <entityname.腐败机械>Corrupt Machinery</entityname.腐败机械>
  <entityname.sz>sand dream+砂塵の彼方へ…</entityname.sz>
  <entityname.zszg>True Coffin</entityname.zszg>
  <entityname.bjzc>Tragic City Eloreno</entityname.bjzc>
  <entityname.kl1>Charon One</entityname.kl1>
  <entityname.kl2>Charon Two</entityname.kl2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_helmet>Plague Protection Helmet</entityname.tsm_eyi_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_suit>Plague Protection Suit</entityname.tsm_eyi_suit>
  <afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>Virus Dormant Stage</afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>
  <afflictionname.eyiinfection>Plague</afflictionname.eyiinfection>

  <!-- trying to get monsters TL'd -->
  <character.Endwormhusk>Huskworm</character.Endwormhusk>
  <character.巨型捕勾兽>Albino Latcher</character.巨型捕勾兽>
  <character.剑头鲨>Swordhead Shark</character.剑头鲨>
  <character.画皮剑头鲨>Swordhead Shark</character.画皮剑头鲨>
  <character.极具摩洛克>Giant Moloch</character.极具摩洛克>
  <character.魔女的下颚>The Witch</character.魔女的下颚>
  <character.腐败机械>Corrupt Machinery</character.腐败机械>
  <character.CorruptionMachinery>Corrupt Machinery</character.CorruptionMachinery>
  <character.欧罗巴之心>Epicentrum</character.欧罗巴之心>
  <character.末日巨鲸>Doomsday Whale</character.末日巨鲸>
  <character.灭世巨鲸>Killer Whale</character.灭世巨鲸>
  <character.死无对证>Undead Dreadnought</character.死无对证>
  <character.埋骨>Gravekeeper</character.埋骨>
  <character.祈鲸>Wailing Whale</character.祈鲸>
  <character.结晶脊鲸>Crystal Whale</character.结晶脊鲸>
  <character.毁灭>Sabotage</character.毁灭>
  <character.破坏>Destruction</character.破坏>
  <!-- <character.Ship> 
  <character.Ship1> 
  <character.Ship2> 
  <character.Ship> 
  <character.Ship1> 
  <character.Ship2> 
  <character.Ship3>  -->
</infotexts>